

# NGUYỄN VÕ GIA KHẢI

# CUSTOMER SERVICE TEAM LEADER

# **PROFILE**

**29/10/1997** 

🗗 Male

**U** 0962715696

⊠ khaibillbill@gmail.com

Thu Duc District, HCMC

## **OBJECTIVE**

High-performance customer relation supervisor with 4 years of experience in Vingroup. Strong skills include handling complains, project management, closing sales and communicating.

Currently looking for an opportunity to become a manager in 5 years, contribute to company revenue growth.

## **SKILLS**

Office softwares: Excel, Word, Powerpoint, Doc, Meet, Google Calendar

8/10

Handling customer complains 9/10

Managements 8/10

## **EDUCATION**

## **UNIVERSITY OF TECHNOLOGY (HUTECH)**

**BUSINESS ADMINISTRATION** 

04/2015 - 10/2018

Degree classification: Good

## **WORK EXPERIENCE**

## **VINMEC JSC (INTERNATIONAL HOSPITAL)**

**CUSTOMER RELATION SUPERVISOR** 

10/2020 - 1/2023

#### - Main responsibilities:

- · Handling customer complains.
- · Master of Call Center, Reception, Cashier.
- Building and training processes for staffs related to specialism.
- · Coordinating with accountant/marketing department to create new policy.
- · Coordinating with sale department register/terminate contract.
- · Hold a monthly meeting to report the team's performance.
- · Evaluate employees KPIs every quarter.
- · Making plan & organize blood donation event yearly.
- Device Management: POS, Stationery, Printer, Software,...

## - Scope of works:

- · Manage a team of 20 people.
- Report to Customer Relation Manager & COO.

## **VINMEC JSC (INTERNATIONAL HOSPITAL)**

**CUSTOMER RELATION EXECUTIVE** 

10/2018 - 10/2020

#### - Main responsibilities:

- · Call Center.
- · Cashier.
- · Reception.

#### - Scope of works:

**English communication** 8/10

**Negotiation** 

8/10

**Planning** 

7/10

## **CERTIFICATIONS**

### 2018

**Bachelor of Business** Administration - Hutech University

2019

lelts 5.0 - Oxford English

## **INTERESTS**

Football

Reading Jogging

Singing

## **HONORS & AWARDS**

2021

Employee of the Year -Vinmec JSC

Report to Customer Relation Supervisor & Customer Relation Manager.

## **QLAND REAL ESTATE LTD**

**SALES STAFF** 

12/2017 - 10/2018

- Main responsibilities:
  - Find potential customer via post advertisings on Real estate.
  - · Consult projects, manage customer data.
  - · Explaining contract and close sale to customer.
- Scope of works:
  - Report to Sale Director.

#### **GOLD SOLUTION LTD**

SUPERVISOR OF STRONGBOW ADVERTISING

06/2017 - 12/2017

- Main responsibilities:
  - Manage promotions to give gift for customers in Karaoke, Restaurants,...
  - · Manage Promotion Girls (take photo for report, control promotion program, support for owner).
- Scope of works:
  - · Report to Marketing manager.

# **ACTIVITIES**

## **VINMEC JSC (INTERNATIONAL HOSPITAL)**

**CONTRIBUTING PERFORMANCES TO COMPANY EVENTS (SINGER)** 

2018 - 2022

## **VINMEC JSC (INTERNATIONAL HOSPITAL)**

**COMPLETED THE 10KM RACE EVENTS** 

2022 - 2022

© topcv.vn